kaki narase sonzai wo
rock away your existence
koko ni iru to
shouting that you are here
arata na tabi ga ima hajimaru
a new journey begins now
kawari yuku kisetsu no naka wo ikinuku tabi ni bokura
as we survived through the changing seasons
chie to tsuyosa wo te ni ireta kedo JUST LOOKS LIKE SURVIVAL GAME
we gained knowledge and strength (just looks like a survival game)
nagareteku jikan no naka ni
but the forgotten memories
okizari ni shita omoi wo
of the feelings abandoned within the flows of time
wasureta koto sura wasurete ita
have also been lost
kuzure kaketa toki kodoku wo shitte
when sinking down we learned loneliness
deaeta bokura hitori ja nai
but now we've met each other we are no longer alone
sarake dase kanjou wo banjou no omoi wo
unveil your feelings those high emotions
namidame ga unmei wo kaete yuku
those tears will change your fate
yami ni uchi narase kodou wo
pound your heartbeat against the darkness
kitto aeru yo onaji itami no hata no moto de
we're sure to meet under the same flag of pain
A coup d'etat at the Land of Green?
Yes, it seems there's no mistake.
The retainers conspired
with some men
and began a rebellion.
What happened to Naruto
and the others?
Speculating from their gathering point,
they are around here.
So, they've already crossed the border.
The large countries have agreed
to make this a demilitarized zone.
Considering Naruto
and the other's mission,
they should be in a safe area.
Are you sure?
What do you mean?
Don't you think
the timing of this request
strangely overlaps with the coup d'etat?
Then you're saying that Naruto's mission
is also related to this case?
There is a possibility.
But there's no time to deal
with Naruto at the moment.
We have to take back
the Land of Green
from the rebels as soon as possible.
If we leave it like this,
the flames of the war will
eventually reach other countries.
True.
Shizune, gather the free villagers
and have them head
to the Land of Green immediately!
Yes, ma'am!
The Byakugan Saw It!
The blind Spot of the Magnet User
You've done it now!
What a persistent brat!
You shouldn't be able to stand anymore.
Naruto!
This is nothing.
What a surprise... You got some guts.
Then, take this, too!
Ninja Art Magnet!
Electromagnetic Illusion.
Naruto!
It's useless!
Your voice can't reach him!
The human brain functions by
a faint electric current
running through it.
If you receive
my magnetic force powder,
it's going to alter your electric current
and stop your thinking.
That chain also has
a strong magnetic force.
Now, get buried!
Naruto!
Are you okay?
Thank goodness.
Hinata... run!
I can't leave you behind.
He is...
He's someone
that you can't deal with.
Naruto, I promise I'll save you!
Hinata!
I'll have you tell me
where that girl is!
Byakugan!
Take this!
Electromagnetic Illusion!
Protective 8 Trigrams 64 Palms!
What?!
I see, so that is the Byakugan
of the Village Hidden in Leaves.
How interesting!
What wonderful Taijutsu, but...
I'll crush it with my power!
I did it...?
Yeah, right.
That level of Taijutsu will not work!
It's useless.
This is bad.
You're not much of a challenge.
I'm disappointed.
Now, tell me,
where did you hide that girl?
If you answer me, I'll let you live.
That boy, too.
If you rescue him right now,
he won't die.
Run... Hinata.
Now say it!
You don't want to save that boy?
Or do you think you can beat me?
If I say it,
Naruto would never forgive me.
Then I'll force you to talk!
I'll change the area behind you
into a powerful magnet.
I can change the position of the magnet
according to your movement.
So, it's a waste to run away!
That brat...
She evaded the attack by throwing
a paper bomb at that very instant.
She's pretty quick-witted.
But...
I won't let you go!
Hinata.
Naruto, I promise
that I'll return to rescue you!
But there is a huge difference
in power between him and me.
I could never beat him!
He's already caught up to me.
What should I do?
This is... iron sand?
I see, his Jutsu can change his body
and the things he touches
into magnets.
The reason why he didn't attack
back there
was to brush off the iron sand
from his body.
If he doesn't,
he would sink right into it.
His attack pattern consists
of alternating between
Ninja Art Magnet
and Iron Sand Genjutsu.
He does this to turn
his magnet powers on and off,
so his body won't completely turn
into a magnet.
Then, there is a way to beat him!
Now, playtime is almost over!
It's time you give up now!
I will never give up!
Because that is my Ninja Way!
What a waste.
How dare you do that to Naruto!
I will definitely not forgive you!
Once you say where that girl is,
why don't you live
with that brat in hell!
Hey, don't be shy and come closer!
Right now!
I'll risk everything
in this single attack!
An attack that didn't work before
will never work!
Is that right?
What?!
We're both going to hell!
Let go, you!
You brat! How dare you play
around with me!
I changed my mind.
I'll finish you off now!
What is this?!
Just now...
I struck a Chakra Point
that would make
your Chakra flow go out of control.
Now your body will turn
into a strong magnet.
What...? That's why you brought me
to this sandy area?!
Stop!
I did it... Naruto.
Damn! I can't move!
The Human Boulder!
Naruto!
Choji!
Are you okay, Naruto?
Thanks, Yurinojou.
So, what happened?
The second Janin attacked
and beat me up.
What happened to Hinata
and the princess?
Oh, yeah! I can't stay here!
What...?
What's going on, Naruto?
Hinata is in danger!
— Oh, Naruto!
— Naruto!
Hinata!
Are you okay, Hinata?
Hang in there, Hinata!
Naruto... Choji...
Yurinojou...
You guys...
You guys came to my rescue.
Of course. We're friends, right?!
Yes.
By the way, that magnet guy...
Where did he go?
He probably sank into the sand.
What?! You did it, Hinata?!
Yeah... I did my best.
Hinata, you're great.
The guy that I couldn't handle...
You're complimenting me?
Naruto.
Here.
This is my forehead band?
The mission is not over yet.
Naruto, please protect the princess...
Princess Haruna.
Hinata...
I promise you!
I swear on this forehead band,
I will definitely protect the princess!
And...
I can't be losing against you!
Naruto.
Look after Hinata, Choji. Yurinojou!
Right!
Leave it to us, Naruto!
Well, I'll be damned.
I can't believe that Ruiga
and Jiga were both defeated.
Well, that saves some trouble though.
Nobody has ever escaped
from my Jutsu.
Today will be a good day.
Haruna! Where are you?!
There she is!
Haruna! Get ahold of yourself!
Are you okay?
I'm glad.
It's me, Princess Haruna!
Naruto.
I came to rescue you,
but what is this treatment?
Sorry.
Why did you escape by yourself?
I can't count on you guys.
I will try to survive,
no matter who's sacrificed.
As long as I survive,
the Land of Green can be revived.
That's the most important thing, right?!
I am a victim!
If I declare that, other countries will
lend me their power.
If I take back the country and...
I, the true successor,
become the feudal lord,
then people will definitely gather
and the Land of Green will return
to the way it was!
I don't think so.
You're saying
that the Land of Green won't revive?!
I'm not saying that.
But I just thought, what if I lived
in the Land of Green...?
If I was a Ninja just like Yurinojou...?
I won't guard a feudal lord like you.
Naruto!
What do you know?!
What do you know about me?!
What do you know about my life
as a hostage?!
Under watch 24-7,
not even allowed to have
my own free time.
I was lonely everyday.
Because of that lifestyle,
I became sick and was in bed
for a long time.
I was finally able to return home
after being close to dying.
Naruto! If you're saying
that I'm wrong, then answer me!
Were the things done to me
in the name of protecting
the Land of Green all wrong?!
Then why did my father and mother
send me away as a hostage?!
Answer me! Naruto!
I won't count on you.
I will go by myself.
Wait. I will go, too.
I promised Hinata that I will
definitely protect you, princess.
With Hinata...?
She fought with the second Janin
and got hurt badly.
Hinata did...?
You guys said that you didn't accept
the mission of protecting me.
Then, why do you concern yourselves
with me?
I...
Not only me,
but Hinata and Choji, too.
We don't like it when somebody
before us is hurt or sad. That's all.
Well, let's go!
If we pass through the valley ahead of us,
we'll get to the town.
If we do that, they probably won't
chase us all the way there!
Please be careful.
No one uses this deer path.
This should shake them.
I found you!
It's impossible...
to run away from me!
Choji?!
Don't make useless efforts.
I'll make you guys my hostages!
You guys take them back to the castle!
Yes!
If you wander around me,
you might get caught
in my Jutsu and die.
That's it. We're almost there!
There's no time to waste! Let's go!
Okay!
Haruna!
I'm okay!
Oh, no!
What is this?!
I see, you have good sense
to dodge that attack!
Who is it?! Where are you?!
Here, over here!
Too bad, but you guys won't be able
to reach that village.
Since you guys are going to die here!
kinou wa Call Sign zenbu keitai de
yesterday's call sign was broadcast all from my phone
norenai Fuzz Guitar henna kouen de
in a strange park I play the fuzz guitar without enthusiasm
Yellow Moon
yellow moon
ima mo mittsu kazoete me wo akete
even now, counting to three I open my eyes
Shadow Moon mada yume wo miteru
shadow moon, I am still dreaming
me wo mite me wo mite se wo mukeai nagara
look at my eyes, look at my eyes, as we face one another's back
me wo mite itsu aeru
look at my eyes, when can we meet?
Every Day Every Night omoi tsuku kotoba de
every day, every night, with every word I can think of
chirakatta mama no kimochi wo ima sugu
right away, my messy feelings as is
mahou no Chord Change nemurenai machi
a magical chord change in a restless city
higawari na Jazz Guitar sotto mainaa de
a daily jazz guitar played in a soft minor key
Damn! He is so troublesome!
How dare he use many
showy attacks.
There is no way I can retaliate!
I've gotta do something.
At this rate, I'm gonna get cornered
and shot.
But even if I wanted to hide,
Haruna's legs are...
Oh, damn it!
What in the world should I do?!
Next time:
"Death Sentece. Cloudy with a Chance of Sun."